いつの間にか
石仮面を 隠し持っているなんて｡
赤石を はめちまっているなんて！
N-No!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)お… おお… 神様…｡
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)カーズ…｡
♬～
I-I didn't see him holding the mask.
はっ！
I didn't see him put the Red Stone in!
Dear God...
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
Cars...
♬ 静寂の底から
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
♬ 深紅の血潮が
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 25: "Birth of the Ultimate Being"
う… うう…｡
ああ…｡
(兵士たち)ああ…｡
(兵士１)あ… ああ…｡
(兵士２)立ち上がった！
He-He stood up!
う… うろたえるんじゃあない！
Stand your ground! German soldiers are not cowards!
ドイツ軍人は うろたえない！
究極の生物だと!? バカな！
The ultimate being?
Madness! No creature could ever become perfect!
完全なる生物になど
なれるものか！
カーズ…｡
Cars...
見ろ！ やつの腕を！
Look at his arm! It's still smoking!
波紋の傷の煙が まだ噴き上げて➡
どんどん
体の方へ上っていくぞ！➡
The Ripple will ruin him!
He'll melt where he stands!
波紋で どんどん溶けていく！➡
やつは
赤石の石仮面をかぶっても➡
He might have put the Red Stone into the mask,
ちっとも！ 全然！
but he is still utterly the same!
前と
違っちゃあいないイイイイーッ！
あのまま くたばるんだァーッ！
And he'll die like that!
(兵士たち)おお…｡
Fire the UV amplifier again!
もう一度 紫外線照射装置を！
We'll end him for sure this time.
今度こそ
完全に 消滅させてやる！➡
準備 急げェー！
(兵士３)はっ！
Hurry it up!
Sir!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
あいつ どうしちゃったんだろ｡
What's going on with him?
ん？
(ﾌｸﾛｳの鳴き声)
(ﾘｽの鳴き声)
What is he staring at?
何を見ているんだ？ カーズは｡
L-Look!
あ… あれを… 見て！ あれを！
See? Over there!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
な… 何だ!? ありゃあ！
(ﾘｽの鳴き声)
Am I seeing things? His hand turned into a squirrel!
幻覚… か？
カーズの腕が リスに！
(ﾘｽの鳴き声)
ヘヘヘ…
何か かわいい気がするな｡
It's kind of cute, actually.
Look out!
ヤバい！ 何か ヤバいぞ！
そのリスに 気を付けろ！
It's dangerous! Stay away from that squirrel!
あっ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ･ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)えっ!?
(一同)うわ～！
(ﾘｽの吠える声)
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
うぉぉ！ リスがァァァ！
The squirrel!
ギニャアアアアアア！
Get out of here! Hurry!
逃げろ！ 早く！
(兵士たち)うわ～！
アアアア！ オグァッ！
Unbelievable! He can manipulate life at will!
なんと！
やつは 生命を自由にできるのか！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)むう！
ああっ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)やった！
Alright!
おおっ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)夜明けだ！
The sun is rising!
(吸血鬼たち)
うぎゃああああああああああ～！
The vampires...
吸血鬼たちが…｡
はっ！
カーズは 太陽の光に弱い｡➡
The sunlight will take care of Cars. We're saved!
助かった…｡
おお…｡
はぁ…｡
あっ！
ああっ！
駄目だ カーズが！
It's no good. Cars is...!
He's still standing, even under the sun!
太陽を背にして 太陽の光の中に！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)フフフフ…➡
ハハハ…｡
おお… なんてことだ…
いか～ん！
This is a nightmare! It can't be!
ああ… 大変なことに！
絶対に まずい！
This looks like our doom!
フフ… フフフ…｡
究極の生命とは➡
A perfect life form combines the abilities of all other life forms.
あらゆる生物の
全ての能力を身に付け➡
It combines all life into one.
全ての生命を兼ねる｡ そして！➡
But this...
Breathtaking. Such beautiful radiance.
美しい！ なんという輝き！➡
That light is the most beautiful thing I've seen.
今まで見た何よりも
すばらしい！➡
あの太陽を ついに！
ついに 克服したぞ！➡
And now I have conquered it.
フハハハ！
や… やつは 無敵になった！
弱点は もう ない｡
H-He's invincible!
He has no weaknesses! Even the Ripple won't work on him!
恐らく
波紋も やつには効かない！
不老不死！ 不死身！
誰も倒せない！➡
He's immortal! Unstoppable! No one can beat him!
He is complete! Cars, the Ultimate Being, is born!
完全なる生物！➡
究極の生命体カーズの誕生だ！
T-This is my fault.
お… 俺のせいだ｡
俺が やつに 赤石の石仮面を
かぶせてしまったんだ！
I let him put on the mask with the Red Stone in it.
Is... Is there no way to stop him?
も… もう あいつを倒すすべは
何もないのか…｡
僕たち人間は➡
Are we humans destined to die, to become food for him?
あいつの食料になって
滅びるだけなのか!?
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ふん！
いや 策はあるぜ！
No, I have a plan.
(一同)あっ！
What was that, Jojo?
何だって？ ジョジョ｡
Hold her.
頼むぜ｡
そう｡ たった１つだけ 策はある！
Yeah...
I have one last plan.
A final plan?
｢たった１つだけ｣？
Yeah, I save it for last.
ああ！ 取って置きのやつだ！
｢取って置き｣？
What is it?
はっ！ ジョジョ ま… まさか!?
Jojo, d-do you mean that final plan?
その 取って置きというのは…｡
Listen up! Do it till your last breath!
いいか？
息が止まるまで とことんやるぜ！
｢息が止まるまで｣だと？
どういうことだ!?
Do what until my last breath?
フ… フフ… フフフフ…｡
Run away!
逃げるんだよ～！
Dammit, I knew it!
うわ～！
やっぱり そうだった～！
ハァァァーッ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)もう 波紋戦士など
どうでもいい！➡
Ripple-users mean nothing to me now.
But you...
だが 貴様だけは けじめだ｡➡
ワムウやエシディシの
復しゅうであり➡
Wham and AC/DC need to be avenged, and I must celebrate!
このカーズの 新しい誕生祝い！➡
Jojo, your death...
ジョジョ！ 貴様だけは➡
どうしても
今 殺さなくてはならない！
...will be dedicated to my birth!
げっ うわ～！ 追いつかれる！
He's catching up!
Pipe down!
騒ぐな！
今 走りながら
策を考えるんだから➡
I'm trying to think up with something! Keep quiet!
静かにしてくれ！
うう… ああっ！ ああ～！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ…➡
Jojo's going out there to save Lisa Lisa and the rest of us!
リサリサや わしらを
助けるために…➡
しかし…｡
駄目だ！ いくら策を練ろうと
あのカーズには勝てん！
But it's useless! No plan of his could overcome what Cars has become!
うわ～！ 来るよ！ 早く 早く！
He's coming! Hurry!
Hey, Smokey!
おい！ こら スモーキー！
必死こいて 走ってるけれど➡
I don't think you understand, so I'll tell you something!
分かってないようだから
１つ 教えとくがな！
お前は わざわざ➡
There's no reason for you to be running with me!
何も 俺と一緒になって
逃げなくったっていいんだぜ！
今 やつは 俺だけ殺そうと
追ってきてるんだ！
Cars is after my blood alone!
He thinks killing me is the best way to celebrate his new life!
この俺を
自らの手で 始末することが➡
新しい自分の 幕開けの儀式だと
思ってるんだからな！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョ どうしても
言っておくことがあるんだ！
Jojo, there's something you have to hear!
Lisa Lisa, your teacher, she's your...
あの リサリサって女の人は！
あの 女の人は！ 君の…！
あっ 来た！
来た 来た 来た 来た 来た！
He's here! He's here!
Speedwagon, is he...?
スピードワゴン… あれが…➡
Is he really the perfect being?
あれが 本当に
究極生命体なのか？
Yes, the power of the Red Stone made him into the ultimate life form!
ああ｡
カーズは 赤石によって➡
究極の 完全なる生物に
変身していくのだ！
A perfect being is: One, invincible.
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)〈完全生物とは➡
１つ 無敵なり！
２つ 決して老いたりせず！➡
Two, does not age.
３つ 決して死ぬことはない！➡
Three, will not ever die.
Four, has the abilities of all other life forms, and outperforms them.
４つ あらゆる生物の能力を
兼ね備え➡
しかも その能力を上回る！➡
そして その形は
ギリシャの彫刻のように➡
In addition, it is like a Greek statue, a model for beauty.
美しさを基本形とする！〉
や… やつを倒す方法は
もう 何もない！
T-There's no way to stop him now.
何一つ 弱点はない！
He has no weakness at all!
Humans can't kill him, not with the Ripple or even the sun!
もう 人間には！
波紋でも 太陽でも➡
あの生物は 殺せない！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ…｡
Jojo!
Smokey, your path ends here!
スモーキー！
お前は ここまでだ！
えっ!?
話は 後で聞くぜ！
Tell me about it later!
Jojo!
ジョジョ～！
フッ… 無駄なことを｡
That won't save you.
ハッハー！
パワー比べをするか！ カーズ！
Let's see who's stronger, Cars!
♬～
おお！ あれは!?
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)我が軍の専用機！
That's...
One of our warplanes!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)んぐあ～！
Jojo!
ジョジョ～！
♬～
ふん…｡
(銃声)
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ぬっ…｡
〈羽は アルマジロの甲羅のように
硬質化し➡
The feathers are as hard as armadillo shell.
They are coated in an oil that deflects bullets.
表面に光る油で 弾丸を滑らせ
方向をずらす｡➡
Naturally, their hardness makes them weapons as well as shields.
当然 防御だけが目的でなく➡
あくまで
攻撃のための硬質化なのだ！〉
ぐっ！
His feathers are like knives!
羽を ナイフみてえに
撃ってきやがった！
ううっ｡
This looks bad!
やはり 駄目か｡
しかし！
But...
I got on this plane to get away from you!
初めから 逃げるために
飛行機に乗ったんだぜ！
♬～
Jojo!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョ～！
ああ もう ジョジョにできるのは
逃げることだけだ！
All he can do now is run!
That's right. Run, Jojo!
そうだ！ 逃げろ ジョジョ！
That's all we humans can do now.
人間に残された道は
もう それしかない｡
時速240km｡ ふぅ…｡
Current speed: 240 km/h.
いくら 究極だろうと完全だろうと
生物は やはり生物｡
No matter how evolved he might be, he's still just an animal.
I'm safe for now.
ほっとしたぜ｡
この飛行機と 同じスピードで
連続飛行するのは無理なようだな｡
I guess he can't keep up with a plane for long.
あっ！ 燃料は…｡
The fuel!
Two hours left.
約２時間分｡
２時間は やつから
逃げられるってことか｡
So I can run away for two hours.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)バカが！➡
Does that fool think he can run from me for even a moment?
このカーズから いっときでも
逃げられると思っているのか？
フフフ もう 貴様は
決して 着陸することはできぬ｡➡
You'll never land safely now.
You won't stand on the earth again.
二度と 自分の足で
大地を踏むことはできないのだ！
Jojo! Jojo!
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョジョ！ ジョジョ！➡
Do you read me? Respond, Jojo!
聞こえるか？
応答せよ！ ジョジョ！
よお スピードワゴンのじいさん！
Hey, Speedwagon!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おお！ ジョジョ！➡
Jojo! Grabbing that plane was a smart move!
飛行機に乗ったのは
賢明だったぞ！
The Germans and I will do what we can to help you get away!
我々やドイツ軍は お前を
逃がすために 全力を尽くす！
Do you have a map?
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)航空図はあるか？
It's right here.
ああ｡ あるぜ｡
Good. Maintain radio contact.
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
よし｡ この無線を決して切るな｡➡
これから 作戦を伝える｡
これは…｡
I'll give you the plan.
What's this?!
First, give us your current position.
ジョジョ！
まず 現在の位置を教えてくれ｡
(無線のﾉｲｽﾞ)
ジョジョ 聞こえてるか？
Jojo, do you read me?
どうした？ おい！
What's wrong? Hey!
Jojo, respond! Jojo!
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ！
返事をしろ！ ジョジョ！
ああ｡ 聞こえているよ｡
Yeah, I read you.
But Speedwagon, no technique or weapon will work on Cars?
なあ スピードワゴンのじいさん｡
カーズには どんな術も
どんな兵器も通じない｡
不死身の完全生物と
言ってたが…｡
You said he was immortal?
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ああ そうだ｡
だから お前が言ったとおり➡
Yeah, I did. Your plan to run is all we can do.
逃げるのが 最善の策！
じいさん！ このジョジョには
アイデアがあるぜ！
Listen up, old man. I have a different idea.
えっ!?
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)アイデア!?
An idea?
おい！ ジョジョ！
余計なことはするな！
Now Jojo, don't do anything rash!
Just keep away from him!
逃げることだけを考えろ！
No! We won't be able to stop him later!
(無線:ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)いや
やつを倒すのは 今しかねえぜ！
駄目だ！ 自分１人で➡
Stop it! Don't even think of doing something on your own!
何かをするなんてことを
考えるな！
Just listen to me, okay?
いいから聞いてくれ！ いいか！
He's the ultimate being on earth!
やつは この地球に現れた
完全生物！
But he's from Earth. This planet gave him life.
しかし その地球なら！
生命を誕生させた この地球なら➡
And it might take him back!
あの生物を
葬ってくれるかもしれねえ！
What? The Earth?!
何？ 地球…？ バカな！
How would the Earth take him back?
地球が 一体 どうやって…｡
Magma!
(無線:ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)マグマだ！
地球最大のエネルギー マグマ！
Magma, the hottest thing on earth!
I'll drive him into the lava at Vulcano Island to kill him!
イタリアの
ヴォルガノ島火山の溶岩に➡
やつを突っ込んで
ぶっ殺してやるぜ～！
い… いかん！
D-Don't! You've risked your life more than enough times!
お前は もう これ以上
危険なことはやらんでいい！
Let us and the Germans handle it!
あとは 我々やドイツ軍に任せろ！
Listen to him, Jojo! Don't be crazy! Cars will kill you!
(無線:ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
そうだよ ジョジョ！➡
むちゃは 駄目だ！
カーズに殺される！
いや！ もう火山は機体の下だぜ！
今しかねえ！
Sorry, I can already see the volcano.
The time is now!
スピードワゴンさん！
Mr. Speedwagon...
It's happening again...
また… なのか？➡
ジョナサンの父親
ジョナサン そしてジョージ…｡
Jonathan's father, Jonathan and George...
The men of the Joestar family all led short lives.
《ジョースター家の男は
代々 短命の伝統》
ああ…
わしは お前まで失いたくはない！
I don't want to lose you, too!
やめてくれ！ ジョジョ！
リサリサのためにも！
Please stop, Jojo!
For Lisa Lisa's sake, too!
Lisa Lisa is your mother!
リサリサは
お前のお母さんなのだよ！
What was that? Say again!
何だって？ 今 何て言った？
(物音)
何の音だ？ これは｡
What is that noise?
ぎっぎゃあ～！
This is insane!
信じらんねえ！
Piranhas?! What the hell?!
ピラニアか？ 一体!?
They're chewing up the plane!
飛行機を食い破っている！
How did they get in?!
どこから入って… はっ！
Cars' feathers from earlier!
さっきのカーズの羽！
They transformed!
あれが 変身したのか！
ああっ！
Damn it! My parachute!
ちくしょう！ パラシュートを！
ふざけるな！
You assholes!
Wh-What now?!
な… なんてこった｡
ぐあっ！
うあ～っ！
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ～！
Jojo!
What's going on? Respond!
どうした？ 返事をしろ！
Jojo!
ジョジョ！
(無線:ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョジョ！ ジョジョ！
Jojo! Jojo!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)フフフ…｡
You're brainless.
バカが｡ そのパラシュートは
貴様にとって➡
That parachute is like a spider's web trapping you, Jojo.
まるで クモの巣だな ジョジョ｡
You're just a little butterfly.
貴様は クモの巣に引っ掛かった
チョウだ！
フフフ…
ゆっくりと 取り殺してくれるわ！
I'll take my time killing you!
はっ！ 何？➡
What?!
I-It's a dummy!
に… 人形!?
うう… はっ！
Cars! This Jojo isn't going down without a fight!
カーズ！
この ジョジョ！
ただでは死なねえぜ！
You're going with me into that volcano!
てめえを道連れで
火口に突っ込んでやるぜ！
Jojo!
ジョジョ！
NUAHHHH 貴様！
うお～！
Damn you!
ぬう！ お… おのれ！
Lunatic!
《エリナおばあちゃん…➡
Granny Erina, you told me about my grandfather once.
一度だけ おじいちゃんのことを
話してくれたっけ｡➡
エリナおばあちゃんを救うために
宿敵ディオと共に➡
You said he sank into the Atlantic with his lifelong foe Dio to save you.
大西洋に散ったって》
《おばあちゃんを
また 悲しませちまうが…》
I hate to sadden you again.
But I guess this is the Joestar blood in me.
《俺も ジョースター家の血筋
ってわけか》
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ふん！
Did you really think I couldn't get away before you hit the ground?
このカーズが
このまま 地面に激突する前に➡
この鉄板を抜いて 機から
離れられないとでも思ったか｡
Cars!
カーズ！
フフフ…｡
死ぬのは お前１人だ
ジョジョ！
You're dying alone, Jojo!
くっ｡
フフフ…｡
W-What the...?!
こ… これは…➡
ぬっ!?
Cars, this plane will be your coffin.
カーズ｡
この飛行機は 貴様の棺おけよ！
You!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)貴様は!?
シュトロハイム！ ふぅ…｡
Stroheim!
How and when did you get in there?!
お前 そんな所に！ いつの間に…｡
フフン｡ 貴様１人じゃあ
心配だったからな！➡
I wasn't sure you could handle it alone!
It was damn cold in this pontoon!
この 浮きの中は
ちと 寒かったぜ！
ハハハッ お前…｡
You're nuts.
But it's time to jump, Jojo!
それより 飛ぶぞ！ ジョジョ｡
What do you mean "jump"?
何だと!? 飛ぶ!?
But I don't even have a parachute!
飛ぶって パラシュートは
もう使っちまった！
Just shut up and jump out of that plane!
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)いいから
空中へ 飛び出しやがれィィィィ！
くっ…
おおおおおおおおおおお！
(無線のﾉｲｽﾞ)
Jojo, respond!
ジョジョ！ 応答しろ！
何とか… 何とか言ってくれ！➡
Say something! Anything!
Just talk to me, Jojo!
返事してくれ ジョジョ！
ジョジョ…｡
Jojo...
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)くぉぉぉぉぉ！
うぁぁぁぁぁ！
ウグググ…｡
はぁ… はぁ…｡
Stroheim...you crazy bastard.
シュトロ… ハイム？
むちゃなやつ…
俺以上に むちゃくちゃなやつ｡
You're even crazier than me!
し… しかし 礼を言うぜ！
B-But I owe you one.
Y-You look all right, but what about Cars?
ぶ… 無事なようだな…➡
それより カーズは…➡
Did Cars land in the magma?!
カーズは 溶岩へ突っ込んだか!?
(地鳴り)
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ･ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)うあっ！
お… の… れ…｡
You... bastards...
OGooAHHHA！
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
I'll be the roundabout
♬ I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
We spend the day your way
♬ You spend the day away
♬ Call it morning
driving through
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley... hey!
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
there with you
♬～
Next Episode
Did you say "the Ripple"?
That's the power of the Earth for you!
Don't you wish to purge your fears?!
Jojo!
Farewell, everyone.
Episode 26:
"The Man Who Became A God"
(ｶｰｽﾞ)波紋疾走だと!?
さすが 地球のエネルギー！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)あらゆる恐怖を
なくしたいと思わないのか!?
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)ジョジョ～！
みんな あばよ…｡